{
    "name": "",
    "isFavorite": false,
    "cards": [
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Chair",
            "back": "Sandalye"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Table",
            "back": "Masa"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Bed",
            "back": "Yatak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Pillow",
            "back": "Yastık"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Blanket",
            "back": "Battaniye"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Couch",
            "back": "Kanepe"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Lamp",
            "back": "Lamba"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Shelf",
            "back": "Raf"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Mirror",
            "back": "Ayna"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Clock",
            "back": "Saat"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Fridge",
            "back": "Buzdolabı"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Oven",
            "back": "Fırın"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Sink",
            "back": "Lavabo"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Toilet",
            "back": "Tuvalet"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Shower",
            "back": "Duş"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Curtains",
            "back": "Perdeler"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Floor",
            "back": "Zemin"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Wall",
            "back": "Duvar"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Ceiling",
            "back": "Tavan"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Fan",
            "back": "Vantilatör"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Television",
            "back": "Televizyon"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Remote",
            "back": "Kumanda"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Carpet",
            "back": "Halı"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Mat",
            "back": "Paspas"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Trash can",
            "back": "Çöp kutusu"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Broom",
            "back": "Süpürge"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Vacuum",
            "back": "Elektrikli süpürge"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Bucket",
            "back": "Kova"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Mop",
            "back": "Paspas"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Iron",
            "back": "Ütü"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Ironing board",
            "back": "Ütü masası"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Washing machine",
            "back": "Çamaşır makinesi"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Dryer",
            "back": "Kurutucu"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Dishwasher",
            "back": "Bulaşık makinesi"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Cup",
            "back": "Bardak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Glass",
            "back": "Cam bardak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Plate",
            "back": "Tabak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Spoon",
            "back": "Kaşık"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Fork",
            "back": "Çatal"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Knife",
            "back": "Bıçak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Pot",
            "back": "Tencere"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Pan",
            "back": "Tava"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Stove",
            "back": "Ocak"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Microwave",
            "back": "Mikrodalga"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Kettle",
            "back": "Su ısıtıcısı"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Toaster",
            "back": "Tost makinesi"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Blender",
            "back": "Blender"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Cupboard",
            "back": "Mutfak dolabı"
        },
        {
            "level": 0,
            "front": "Drawer",
            "back": "Çekmece"
        }
    ]
}
